# DEJAY ODUJOKO

INTEGRATIONS DEVELOPER

+8167854438



dejavxtrem@hotmail.com



Fayetteville, AR



linkedin.com/in/Adedeji-odujoko



## **EDUCATION**

ENTERPRISE SYSTEMS, MS University of Arkansas, Arkansas 2016 - 2017

INTERNATIONAL BUSINESS, MSC Conventry University, UK 2012 - 2014

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Data Analytics

Javascript

Python

HTML5/CSS

Nodejs

ExpressJS

ReactJs

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

(Clarify & Harmony)

Code Academy (Build Front-End Web Apps from Scratch) Code Academy (Build Web APIs from Scratch) Code Academy (Build Websites from Scratch)

Cleo Certified Clarify EDI Developer

## PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

An innovative and motivated individual with the ability work in a fast paced, multi-tasking environment and produce a high standard of work. Competence with multiple programming languages, including JavaScript, Python, NodeJS, React, HTML, CSS, Linux, and shell scripting. Experience with Electronic Data Interchange (EDI) in IT and EDI translations. Extensive exposure to the full B2B integration process, Enterprise Applications, and communication protocols.

## **EXPERIENCE**

JBHUNT TRANSPORT | ARKANSAS | 2019 - Present

#### **EDI ANALYST**

- Conducts minor Electronic Data Interchange mapping enhancements and changes.
- Assists Electronic Data Interchange admins in any functions where necessary
- Map and convert X12 documents to XML, JSON, and CSV for inbound and outbound document series.
- Assists in verification of communication connections.
- Integrate with trading partners via REST, SOAP and EDI.

SUPPLYPIKE | ARKANSAS | 2017 - 2019

# INTEGRATION DEVELOPER

- Analyze and translate business requirements into technical solutions.
- Develop and implement solutions to integrate applications across SupplyPike.
- Map and convert X12 documents to XML, JSON, and CSV for inbound and outbound document series.
- Make strong analytical, conceptual, and problem-solving decisions.
- Integrate with trading partners via REST, SOAP and EDI.
- Configure and set up AS2, FTP, SMTP, TCP/IP, VAN and PDBC connections.
- Coordinate teams from various CPGs, VANs, carriers, warehouses, and other supply chain partners in setting up and testing multiple transaction sets.
- Attention to both the technical details and the big picture (business) impact).
- Consistently met established internal goals for on-time delivery and error rates.

EDI Academy (EDI 850, 856, ASN and UCC-128 labels)

EDI Academy (EDI Enveloping & Structure)

EDI Academy (EDI connectivity AS2, VAN, FTP)

CompTIA A+ Certified Technician

## **EXPERTISE**

Web Development
B2B Integration
Enterprise Sysytems
EDI Translation
Web Application
EDIHQ Translation Software
Cleo Harmony and Clarify

### **INTERESTS**

Gaming
Traveling
Long Tennis
Sports (Soccer)

## **EXPERIENCE**

K12 UK Limited | UNITED KINGDOM | 2015 – 2015 FINANCE AND ADMIN ASSISTANT

- Processed and reconcile purchase and sales ledger transactions and monthly head office bank reconciliations.
- Maintained computerised and manual bookkeeping accounting and recording filing systems through the use of FMS and SAGE 50 Accounts 2014
- Ensured all purchase invoices are properly coded, posted to the ledger and authorised for payment.

GOTBOX22 STORAGE | UNITED KINGDOM | 2013 - 2014

ACCOUNT ASSISTANT

- Processed payments and documents such as invoices.
- Journal vouchers, employee reimbursements, and statements.
- Calculate rates paid for purchases and all price extensions.
- Review on-line transactions for changes and accuracy and corrects errors.
- Disbursed funds using manual/local warrants or petty cash and makes changes according to specific instructions..

# **REFERENCES**

Stacy Shemin

EDI Operations Manager

SUPPLYPIKE | ARKANSAS

Stacy@Supplypike.com

479-407-0597

Ethan Nicholson

EDI Analyst

J.B HUNT TRANSPORT | ARKANSAS
501-827-8313